Finding Aid for the Inventory of the American Pain Society Records Biomed.0123
UCLA Library Special Collections
American Pain Society records
1977-1991
UCLA Library Special Collections
American Pain Society
Biomed.0123
5 Linear Feet (5 cubic-foot cartons)
Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Acquisition
The American Pain Society Records were given to the John C. Liebeskind History of Pain Collection by the American Pain Society in October, 1995.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9942303173606533
History
The American Pain Society (APS) was formed by American clinicians, researchers, and teachers in the field of pain in response to a growing interest in and need for a national pain organization that would also serve as a chapter of the International Association for the Study of Pain. The society was to foster research and education in the multidisciplinary field of pain in the United States.
Organizational work began in 1977, when John J. Bonica, on February 18, sent a letter to twenty-six other key American colleagues asking them to attend a meeting in Chicago just sixteen days later as members of "the Advisory Committee for the founding of the American Pain Society." Despite the short notice, all but six of the invitees attended the meeting. (Bonica missed it as well due to complications from hip surgery.) All motions were unanimously approved: the decision to found a national society compatible with the IASP; the provision for regional, state, or other subgroups; that B. Berthold Wolff-who was co-chairing the meeting along with B. Raymond Fink--should chair a Steering Committee; and that there would be a Membership Committee.
Membership in the Society was initially solicited by Wolff in a letter dated June 28, 1977 and sent to all American members of the IASP and its Eastern and Western Regional Chapters. Ultimately, there were 510 charter members of the Society by the time it was officially inaugurated in December, 1978. The APS had its first Annual Scientific Meeting in San Diego on September 9-10, 1979.
In 1989, 63% of APS members responding to a survey voted that the APS should have its own journal. APS Journal debuted with the Spring 1992 issue and has been published as Pain Forum since 1995.
In the past twenty years, membership has grown to include over 3000 pain professionals.
Scope and Content
The American Pain Society Records represent a period of growth for the Society. Although foundational documents are minimal, the collection features correspondence and records of the activities that built the organization, during the 1980s, into what it is today. These documents include financial papers, committee formations, the records of important general and board meetings, membership building practices, and publication records, including the membership's decision to publish a journal.
The American Pain Society Records were processed in 1998 by David C. Gartrell. The collection is organized into five major series. Brief descriptions of each follow.
Related Material
John C. Liebeskind papers. Unprocessed collection. Material is unavailable for access. Please contact Special Collections reference (spec-coll@library.ucla.edu) for more information.
Pain. (MeSH); Fink, B. Raymond.; International Association for the Study of Pain.; Wolff, B. Berthold.; Bonica, John J.
- Administrative
  Scope and Contents note
  The Administrative series is comprised of such elements as accreditation of the society, committee assignments, elections, correspondence, awards, and pre-1986 "historical" materials. Dates in this series span 1981-1990.
- Committees
  All 1980s meetings and correspondence for the following committees:
  Affiliations, Awards & Certificates, Bylaws, Allied Health Organization, Long Range Planning, Membership, Newsletter, Nominations, Pain Clinics, Pain in the Elderly, Professional Education, Public Information, Regional Sections, Scientific & Professional Ethics, Scientific Program.
- Meetings
  Meetings series leans heavily towards Board of Directors meetings from the late 1980s, though some annual meetings are included.
- Membership
  Membership applications and rosters, criteria for membership, brochures, and unsuccessful applications.
- Publications
  This series covers the various APS publications, including Principles of Analgesic Use in the Treatment of Acute Pain and Chronic Cancer Pain aka Analgesic Guide, the Directory of Pain Management Facilities, and the APS Newsletter. Also represented is the member survey that supported the publication of an APS journal, analgesic guide, directory of pain clinics, APS newsletters.
- Administrative
  - General Issues of Concern. [Requests for information on TENS device], [1988]. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - General Issues of Concern. TENS - Dr. Gershkoff, [1988]. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - General Issues of Concern. IPF Grants, [1987]. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - General Issues of Concern. APS Membership Info/Brochure, [1988]. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - General Issues of Concern. American Academy of Pain Management, [1988]. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - General Issues of Concern. Unethical Pain Clinic Practices, [1988]. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Administrative. [Election results], [1989]. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Administrative. [Correspondence re: finances], [1988]. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Administrative. Committee Lists, [1987-88]. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Administrative. Committee Assignments [one acceptance letter], [1987]. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Administrative. Ad-Hoc Committee Assignments, [1987]. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Administrative. Chronic Pain Treatment Outcome, [1988]. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - [Committee guidelines and appointments], [1983-86]. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Correspondence, 1988. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - President's Correspondence. Committee Reports, [1988]. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - APS General Correspondence, 1981-84. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - NCR--Natl. Comm. for Research in Neurological Disorders, [1985-88]. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - APS Newsletter, [1985-86]. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Marquis Professional Directory, [1983]. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - APS Kerr Memorial Award, [1986]. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Liaison [Committee], [1984-85]. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - APS - C.A.R.F. [Commission on Accreditation of Rehabilitation Facilities], [1982-88]. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - APS - Insurance [possible need for], [1983-84]. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - comm/1989 q.aps.brd [correspondence, primarily Board of Directors], [1989-90]. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - [Committee nominations and appointments], [1985]. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - APS - Committee Appointments, [1981-84]. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - APS - Archives - Carry Forward [correspondence], [1980-83]. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - APS Education, [1984-86]. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - [Committee appointments], [1983-85]. (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Reports/Items for Agenda, [1989]. (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Boards and Committees, 1989. (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - President's Correspondence, [1988]-1989. (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Center for Consumer Health Care Information, [1990]. (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Correspondence, [1988-89]. (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - APS Procedure Manual, [1983-84]. (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. Bylaws., [1981-86]. (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. Bylaws. [Proposed changes], [1986]. (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. Bylaws. [APS Standard Committee Operating Procedures], [1986]. (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. Bylaws. "Master--do not remove", [nd]. (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Bylaws, 1986. (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. IASP [newsletters], [1983-87]. (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. IASP [membership, publications], [1981-87]. (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. Financial Statements, 1984-85, 1984-85. (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. Financial Statement, 1983, 1983. (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. Financial. Treasury - Bills [includes check registry, dues payment list], [1980-82]. (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - APS Historical--Pre 1986. Financial. [Correspondence, taxes, financial agreements], [1980-86]. (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - ACCME - APS - CME Accreditation. Resurvey 1987 [Folder 1 of 3], [1982-86]. (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - ACCME - APS - CME Accreditation. Resurvey 1987 [Folder 2 of 3], [1982-86]. (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - ACCME - APS - CME Accreditation. Resurvey 1987 [Folder 3 of 3], [1982-86]. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - 70519 [form letters and inquiry responses], [1989]. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Pain and Sports Medicine Resonses, [1989]. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Regional Experts Roster, nd. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - TRNS File, [1989]. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Administrative. Board of Directors Lists, [1987-88]. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - PR/ARTICLES, q.aps.mkt, [1987-90]. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - agendas/1990, q.aps.brd, [1990]. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - PRES-ELECT/COMM, q.aps.brd, [1989]. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - COMM/PRES, q.aps.brd, [1989]. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - LRP/COMM, q.aps.brd, [1989-90]. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - COMM/1990, g.aps.brd [note: other folders' letters appear to be lowercase Q; this one is G], 1990. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - COMM/Cmt to Coordinate Activities (ad hoc), q.aps.cmt, [1989]. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - cmt.chairs, q.aps.cmt [committee chairs], nd. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - AWARDS & CERTIFICATES, q.aps.cmt, [1990]. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - prof.educ/accme, q.aps.cmt, [1989-90]. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - [Tiffany & Co. credit acceptance], [1986]. (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Committees
  - Affiliations Committee, Correspondence, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Affiliations Committee, [Correspondence], [1982-85]. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Liaison, Allied Health Organization Committee, Correspondence, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Liaison, Allied Health Organization Committee, Committee Reports, [1987-88]. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Liaison, Allied Health Organization Committee, Medicare Coverage Issues, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Awards & Certificates Committee, [Correspondence], 1986. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Bylaws Committee, [Proposed changes], 1989 [1987-90]. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Bylaws Committee, Committee Reports, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Bylaws Committee, Correspondence, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Bylaws Committee, 5/27/88 APS Bylaws Change, 1988. (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Ethics Committee, [Correspondence], [1985-86]. (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, [Correspondence], [1986]. (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Long Range Planning Committee, [Chicago Meeting, [1986]. (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Membership Committee, [Correspondence and mass mailings], 1989[-90]. (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Membership Committee, Misc. Correspondence, [1987-90]. (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Membership Committee, Correspondence with New Members, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Membership Committee, IASP Member Recruitment, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Membership Committee, Membership Brochure, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Membership Committee, Neuroscience Member Recruitment, nd. (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Membership Committee, Correspondence, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Membership Committee, Membership Directory, [1988-89]. (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Membership Committee, Committee Reports, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Membership Committee, Regional Recruitment, [1987]. (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Membership Committee, Correspondence with New members, 1988. (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Newsletter Committee, [Correspondence], 1989[-90]. (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Nominations Committee, Call for Nominations Correspondence, [1984-88]. (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Nominations Committee, Nominations, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Nominations Committee, Nominating Committee, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Nominations Committee, APS Election Responses from Candidates, [1990]. (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Nominations Committee, Election Announcements '90, Winners/Losers, 1990. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Nominations Committee, APS - Nominating Process, 1990-91. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Nominations Committee, Election Ballot, [1990]. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Nominations Committee, Nominations/Nominees, [1989-90]. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Pain Clinics Committee (Ad Hoc), [Correspondence], 1989. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Pain Clinics Committee, Correspondence w/ Dentistry members, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Pain Clinics Committee, Accreditation Substantiation, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Pain Clinics Committee, General Correspondence, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Pain Clinics Committee, Pain Clinics Questionaire, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Pain in the Elderly Committee (Ad Hoc), [Correspondence}, 1989. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Pain in the Elderly Committee, Correspondence, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - Professional Education Committee, ACCME Accreditation, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Professional Education Committee, Committee Reports, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Professional Education Committee, [Correspondence], 1989[-90]. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Public Information Committee, Medicine for the Layman, Correspondence, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Public Information Committee, Analgesic Guide, Requests for Reprints, [1988-89]. (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Public Information Committee, Analgesic Guide, 2nd Edition, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Public Information Committee, Analgesic Guide, Mailing to AAMC, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Public Information Committee, Analgesic Guide, Requests to Reprint, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Public Information Committee, NUPRIN Report, [1988]. (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Public Information Committee, [Guidelines, correspondence], 1989[-90]. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Public Information Committee, Speakers Bureau, Request for Speaker, nd. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Public Information Committee, Pain Related Articles & TV Broadcasts, [1988]. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Public Information Committee, Public Pain Inquiries, [1988]. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Public Information Committee, Vicente's cc's of Correspondence, [1987-88]. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Public Information Committee, Regional Specialist Roster, [1988]. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Public Information Committee, Analgesic Guide, Purdue Frederick, [1988]. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Public Information Committee, Correspondence, [1987-88]. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Public Information Committee, Misc. Questionnaires, [1989]. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Public Information Committee, Mailing List Requests, [1988]. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Public Information Committee, APS Mailing Lists, [1988]. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Public Information Committee, Speakers Bureau Correspondence, [1987-88]. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Regional Sections Committee, [Correspondence, survey], 1989[-90]. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Regional Sections Committee, APS Regional Groups, [1987]. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Regional Sections Committee, Committee Reports, [1987]. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Scientific & Professional Ethics Committee, [Correspondence], 1989[-90]. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Scientific & Professional Ethics Committee, Committee Reports, [1988]. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Scientific & Professional Ethics Committee, Correspondence, [1987]. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Scientific & Professional Ethics Committee, Committee Reports, [1987]. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Scientific & Professional Ethics Committee, [Correspondence, proposals], 1989 [1988-90]. (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Meetings
  - APS Board Meeting, 4 August 1987 [agenda, reports], [1986-87]. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - APS - Board of Directors Minutes & Agendas, [1980-83]. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - APS Board Minutes - September 1984 [agenda, minutes, ballots], 1984. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - APS Board Agenda - June [? - November] 1984 [minutes, correspondence], 1984. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - [Board of Directors meetings and conference call], [1985]. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - APS Annual Board Meetings October 1985 Minutes; APS Agenda May [11?] Interim Agenda & Exhibits, [1985]. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - [Board of Directors Meeting, Sep 1984; May 1985 Conference Call--minutes, correspondence], [1984-85]. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - [Board of Directors Conference Call, 28 Apr 1986--agenda, minutes], [1986]. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - [Board of Directors Meetings--agenda, minutes, committee and financial reports], [1986]. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - APS Long range Planning Committee, June 12-13, M. Notkin, 1986. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - APS Board Meeting, 4 August [minutes, reports], 1987. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - American Pain Society Board of Directors Meeting, Tape #1, Indianapolis, Indiana, May 4, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - American Pain Society Board of Directors Meeting, Tape #2, Indianapolis, Indiana, May 4, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - American Pain Society Board of Directors Meeting, Tape #3, Indianapolis, Indiana, May 4, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - American Pain Society Board of Directors Meeting, Tape #4, Indianapolis, Indiana, May 4, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - American Pain Society Board of Directors Meeting, Tape #5, Indianapolis, Indiana, May 4, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - [Contracts, 1986 General Scientific Meeting], [1985-86]. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - [Symposium or Workshop Proposals, 1990 Annual Meeting], [1989-90]. (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - [Call for proposals--rejection letters], [1990]. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, [1988]. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Spec Sheets [hotel, audio-visual charges], 1985[-86]. (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - APS Preliminary Program, 1985. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - APS Final Program, [1985]. (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Dallas comm. mtgs., [1984-85]. (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, May 1989, Memos, etc., 1989. (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - May Board Meeting [planning], [1989]. (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Room List, [1989]. (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Dr. Cassoan, International Conference, [1989]. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - PROGRAM MATERIAL, q.aps.conf [abstracts, phone messages, bills, etc.], [1989-90]. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - EXT/OTHER ORG., q.aps.mtg [correspondence, brochures, announcements from other organizations], [1987-90]. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - APS Annual Meeting Profile [registration data], 1985. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Speaker Release Forms [?-speaker lists], [1985-86]. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - [Contracts for October 1985 meeting], [1985]. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - APS '85 Survey [registrant survey responses--demographics and meeting critique], [1985]. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - [Blank registration materials, meeting brouchures], [1989]. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Conference Call, April 28, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, Minutes: Conference Call, April 28, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, November 6, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors Meeting, November 8, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Annual Business Meeting Minutes, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Board of Directors 2/24/88 Conference Call, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - [Executive Committee Conference Call, February 24, Topics for discussion], [1988]. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Annual Meeting, Board of Directors Meeting, 11/11, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting, Board of Directors Meeting, 11/11, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Annual Business Meeting Agenda, 1986. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - MTGS/SPG '90, q.brd [letter with conflicting dates], [1989]. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - minutes, q.aps.brd, 1988-89. (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Membership
  - Certificate Lists [membership and application lists], [1988-89]. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Membership Roster, 1988-89. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Membership Roster, 1984. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Membership Applications, [1987]. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Membership Application, [1987-88]. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - [Balnk membership application packet], [1989]. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - [Items mass-mailed to members], [1981-1986]. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Membership Applications, [1986-87]. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Membership Applications, [1986]. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Membership Applications, [1986]. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Membership Applications, [1986-88]. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Membership Updates, 1989. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Membership Cancellations, 1988. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Lists of New Members, [1988]. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Dead Applications--No Sponsor Letters, [1987-88]. (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Life Membership / APS, [1984]. (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - APS - Membership Comm. & Certificates, [1981-86]. (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Membership Criteria, [1984]. (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - APS Directory [and] Correspondence, [1983]. (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - [Sample APS membership certificate], nd. (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Publications
  - Directory of Pain Management Facilities, 1989. (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Analgesic Guide Correspondence, [1989]. (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - [Analgesic guide orders], [1987-88]. (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Requests to reprint and republish, [1987]. (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Analgesic Guide Order Form, [1990]. (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Correspondence with authors Payne and Max, [1987-88]. (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Correspondence with Authors re: Copyrights, [1987]. (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Legal Correspondence - Disclaimer, [1987]. (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Copyright Information, [1987]. (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Analgesic Guide Correspondence - Suggestions and Criticism, [1987-89]. (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Newsletter [copies], [1985-89]. (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - Newsletter [copies and correspondence], [1988-89]. (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Newsletter, January, Vol. III, No. 1, [1989]. (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - Newsletter, March, [1989]. (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Newsletter, June, 1989. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Journal, APS Journal Survey, [1989]. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Journal, Survey Results, [1989]. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Journal, [Journal Publication Survey--completed forms], [1989]. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Pain Clinics Directory [Folder 1 of 2], [1988-89]. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Pain Clinics Directory [Folder 2 of 2], [1988-89]. (Box 5, Folder 6)